

SUMMARY

A skilled and creative Full Stack web developer with a passion for creating beautiful, responsive, and user-friendly websites. I've worked on a variety of web projects. My goal is to Acquire a Challenging position in environment where I can best utilize my skills and educations.

SKILLS

- Html
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Material UI
- React Js
- Redux
- Core Java
- Spring Boot
- Hibernate
- Mysql
- NodeJs

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Engineering -Computer

Universal College Of Engineering Mumbai

CGPI:- 7.39/10

CERTIFICATION



Java Full Stack Course

Try Catch Institute 2022-2023

LANGUAGES

- English
- Marathi
- Hindi

SWAPNIL MORE

JAVA FULL STACK DEVELOPER

\$9082810431 **★**moreswapnil.619@gmail.com

https://moreswapnil95.github.io/Myportdolio/

O Borivali, Mumbai 400066

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Developer XS CAD LIMITED

08/2023-Present Mumbai

- Collaborate with the development team to understand project requirements and contribute to the design and implementation of frontend solutions.
- Assist in developing and maintaining user interfaces for web applications and websites. Implement responsive designs and ensure cross-browser compatibility.
- Collaborate with backend developers to integrate frontend logic with server-side functionality.
- Skills: Rect Js, Redux, Material UI, Bootstrap.

BackEnd Developer-Intern

09/2023-10/2023

INFOTRIXS

Mumbai

- · creating, maintaining, testing, and debugging the entire back end of an application or system. This includes the core application logic, databases, data and application integration, API.
- Collaborating with the Front-End development team to understand project requirements and implementation of Backend solutions.
- Skills: Spring Boot, Core Java, Hibernate, Mysgl.

PROJECTS

Url-Shorten API

- Url Shortener creates a short link from a very long URL. Clicking on a short URL, the user will be redirected to the original URL.
- It Consist Registration and login api, for Password md5hash method used which conver into hash value. When User logged in it check user is authenticated or not.
- Tech Used: Core java, Spring boot, Hibernate, Mysql
- Source Code: https://github.com/moreswapnil95/UrlShortner.git

Markers on Map

- This helps to create multiples markers on map and on click it shows the data. That data also store in table format.
- Tech Used: React Js, Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap.
- **SourceCode:** https://github.com/moreswapnil95/react-map.git
- Link: https://moreswapnil95.github.io/react-map/

- Selecting options from dropdown menu you can create and delete some part from form. After that you can submit the form and enter the details it shows result in last div.
- Source Code: https://github.com/moreswapnil95/Dynamic-Form.git
- Link: https://moreswapnil95.github.io/Dynamic-Form/

Fruit and Veg. clone website

• Link: https://github.com/moreswapnil95//Grocery-website-clone/